<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog on Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog on Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/en/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Encoder Representation with Matching Task for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/publication/bert-with-matching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 10:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/publication/bert-with-matching/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face adversarial sample</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/adversarial-sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/adversarial-sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The demo of the face attack system based on the adversarial sample (black box attack) is completed, which makes the AWS Face Rekognition system incorrectly classify.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZiYue</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/ziyue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/ziyue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ZiYue is the name of a gold jewelry series that means appaintment between parents and children.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Space</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/cloud-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/cloud-space/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project is a social innovation project that belongs to the intersection of urban science. We are committed to providing the community with public space (e.g., roof space) renewal design and follow-up urban community smart management system integration solution. This project has obtained &lt;strong&gt;the first prizes&lt;/strong&gt; in several entrepreneurial competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembrance</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/seek-memory-album/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/seek-memory-album/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At present, AI technology is developing at a high speed and has achieved remarkable results in the fields of voice, image, and natural language processing. Based on image and video fingerprint technology, we have built a smart cloud photo album platform, which aims to be a good helper for users to quickly and accurately find photoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given main features of the album, we name the platform &lt;code&gt;Remembrance&lt;/code&gt; that is intended to find memories. And the brand slogan is &amp;ldquo;no hard to find memories.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We design the platform logo as a leaf. from the morphological point of view, it can also be understood as a pen made of feathers, which contains the meaning of &amp;ldquo;recording&amp;rdquo;. On the other hand, it is a bookmark made of leaves that helps the owner find the desired photoes in the album.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Title Trigger: All titles you want</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/title-trigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/title-trigger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a project from Google AI ML Winter Camp (2019). In the camp, we developed a NLP Project called &lt;code&gt;Title Trigger&lt;/code&gt;, including extraction &amp;amp; abstraction, generation, text style transferring, etc. in different dimensions, using a bunch of latest technology to achieve the best performance. The training speed was dramatically improved. Finally, our project obtained &lt;strong&gt;Most Technical Award&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WeCup</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/wecup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/wecup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We developed a smart water cup &lt;code&gt;WeCup&lt;/code&gt;, integrating an alarm clock and serverl medicine boxes, to provide a more convenient medication experience for the elderly and young people with medication habits, and change the status quo of “forgetting to take medicine, not wanting to take medicine”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usher Robot</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/rpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/rpi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Prediction</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/stock-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/stock-prediction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is Kaggle data mining competition. By analyzing news data to predict stock prices, Kagglers have a unique opportunity to advance the state of research in understanding the predictive power of the news. This power, if harnessed, could help predict financial outcomes and generate significant economic impact all over the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During that, we developed the stock forecasting system based financial data and news data, using XGboost, Estimation Distribution Algorithm(EDA) and we got top 2% final result around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 20:47:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From now on, you can get some information about me from this website. This is my home.😄&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi Baby</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/hi-baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/hi-baby/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We developed a maternal community platform named &lt;code&gt;Hi Baby&lt;/code&gt; that provides new mothers with communication, diary, baby goods online store, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lan</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/lan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/lan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lan is the name of a clothing series that is wind in the mountain and represents introverted personality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Page</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/tutorial/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/tutorial/example/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my top 10 tips for getting started with Academic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip-1&#34;&gt;Tip 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tip-2&#34;&gt;Tip 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing Image Classification Based On Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/publication/remote-sensing-image-classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 10:28:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/publication/remote-sensing-image-classification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--
More detail can easily be written here using *Markdown* and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.
--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glaze Spraying</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/glaze-spraying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/glaze-spraying/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Glaze spraying is a key process in ceramic production, yet how to make the glaze coating uniform in various situations is a rather confusing issue. We have to set up different models at different times. If we can find a relatively universal strategy, much time can be saved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we adopt elliptic double β distribution model to obtain the thickness cumulative model on planes and solve Issue 1. Then we modify the basic model to make it applicable when dealing with curved surfaces and spheres. In this way, we deal with Issue 2 and 3 successfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As any free-form curved surface can be regarded as a superposition of several basic ruled curved surfaces, combinatorial use of piece-wise approximation and superstition can perfectly generalize our solution above, as shown in Issue 4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use MATLAB simulation to find the optimal solution. Sensitivity analysis of spray thickness and spray gun height is also made.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
