<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mathematical model competition on Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/tags/mathematical-model-competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mathematical model competition on Lingxiao Zhang&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/tags/mathematical-model-competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Glaze Spraying</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/glaze-spraying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/glaze-spraying/</guid>
      <description>Glaze spraying is a key process in ceramic production, yet how to make the glaze coating uniform in various situations is a rather confusing issue. We have to set up different models at different times. If we can find a relatively universal strategy, much time can be saved.
In this paper, we adopt elliptic double β distribution model to obtain the thickness cumulative model on planes and solve Issue 1. Then we modify the basic model to make it applicable when dealing with curved surfaces and spheres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Clustering Based On Communication Data</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/community-clustering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/community-clustering/</guid>
      <description>In this paper, the community clustering problem based on communication data is used to classify the social network, and an effective algorithm for the problem is proposed. A reasonable delivery scheme is given under the premise of satisfying the maximum information coverage and the minimum cost. On this basis, considering the influence of multiple factors, the communication networks given in the question are reclassified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Growth of Cities</title>
      <link>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/smart-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OwenMasculinity.github.io/en/project/smart-city/</guid>
      <description>With the increase of population, more and more people are pouring into cities. The world is rapidly urbanizing. Consequently, urban planning has become increasingly important and necessary to ensure that people have access to equitable and sustainable homes, resources and jobs.
Smart growth focuses on building cities that embraces the E’s of sustainability—Economically prosperous, socially Equitable, and Environmentally Sustainable. To measure how successful the city meets the goal of smart growth, we propose a metric model to identify the degree of smart growth, and evaluate two cities’ metric.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>